Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/wolfgangwanless (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Adobe Creative Suite
Web Development
Video

Certifications

Project Management Simplified

Wolfgang Wanless

Product Praetorian

Denver, Colorado, United States

Summary

My name is Wolfgang Wanless and I'm a creative product engineer.

With over a decade of experience in video, and a growing portfolio of engineering projects, I have been working hard in my niche to help growing businesses get results.

Let's talk about Web, AI, Video, Product, Plastic, or anything new and exciting.

Experience

Boost Infinite
Product Manager
June 2023 - Present (6 months)
Littleton, Colorado, United States

Quorum Recruiting
Head of Product
March 2023 - Present (9 months)

Wonderful Waste Co-Founder April 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months) Denver, CO

Wonderful Waste tackles the problem problem of plastic waste by turning used plastic into useful, sustainable, and recyclable goods. Priorities for Wonderful Waste include sequestering large amounts of plastic from going to landfills, using locally sourced recycled plastic, and creating things that are further recyclable and have long lifespans.

Storyvine, Inc.
Story Engineer II
September 2016 - March 2023 (6 years 7 months)
Greater Denver Area

As a Story Engineer I work with clients and our company to develop and code non linearly captured videos through Storyvine. Storyvine is a video platform that uses an app to guide users through a structured mobile capture, to record video anywhere, anytime. Video is uploaded into the cloud and edited into a polished fully-customized template in near real time for a fraction of the cost of a film crew. Our web based management system allows users to capture content, curate, and manage it in a simple way unlike any other system. Storyvine is the answer for branded video content.

Lumena Software Engineer June 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 3 months) Denver, Colorado, United States

Developed the alpha version of the Lumena kiosk software. Working closely with the Lumena team, I used Windows Presentation Foundation to guide users through the Lumena experience and trigger time sensitive file executions to play both audio and trigger lighting sequences.

Glenarm Restaurants
Courtesy Patrol
September 2015 - July 2016 (11 months)
Denver

Currently carry the title of 'courtesy patrol', whose responsibilities include acting as a doorman, being present for guests on the floor, selling tobacco and alcohol products, and deploying and following safety procedures.

Starbucks
Shift Supervisor
September 2011 - September 2015 (4 years 1 month)
22nd and Sheridan

Worked as a shift manager, including both morning and evening shifts and was responsible for cash control, advanced customer relations, monitoring of labour, costs minimization analysis, and keeping everyone I work with in high spirits. I was praised for my progressed business acumen, my ability to increase store morale, and how quickly I adapted to new roles.

Rockley Family Foundation Sales Associate 2009 - 2011 (2 years) Typically I worked either at the front desk of the foundation greeting customers and getting them set up, or working with the staff members moving instruments for display and for customers. At the beginning and end of each weekend long sale I would help set up and dismantle each of the guitars, keyboards and digital pianos for transport to and from the events.

Denver Open Media Media Intern November 2008 - February 2009 (4 months) Denver

Assisted customers with a variety of needs including managing the television scheduler, operating television equipment, quality assurance to all leased equipment, operating state of the art video editing programs, and some occasional artistic advice.

Education

Regis University
Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science · (2011 - 2015)

Jefferson County Open High School (2007 - 2011)